Edward Dorn Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Correspondence to Edward Dorn, undated, 1956-1993
  - Subseries B: Minor Correspondence, 1962-1993
    - A - F, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 478)
    - G - L, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 479)
    - M - R, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 480)
    - S - Z, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 481)
    - Unidentified Author, 1973 (Box 30:, Folder 482)
    - A - F, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 483)
    - G - L, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 484)
    - M - R, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 485)
    - S - Z, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 486)
    - Unidentified Author, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 487)
    - A - F, 1975 (Box 30:, Folder 488)
    - G - L, 1975 (Box 30:, Folder 489)
    - M - R, 1975 (Box 31:, Folder 490)
    - S - Z, 1975 (Box 31:, Folder 491)
    - Unidentified Author, 1975 (Box 31:, Folder 492)
    - A - F, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 493)
    - G - L, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 494)
    - M - R, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 495)
    - S - Z, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 496)
    - Unidentified Author, 1976 (Box 31:, Folder 497)
    - A - F, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 498)
    - G - L, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 499)
    - M - R, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 500)
    - S - Z, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 501)
    - Unidentified Author, 1977 (Box 31:, Folder 502)
    - A - F, 1978 (Box 31:, Folder 503)
    - G - L, 1978 (Box 31:, Folder 504)
    - M - R, 1978 (Box 31:, Folder 505)
    - S - Z, 1978 (Box 31:, Folder 506)
    - Unidentified Author, 1978 (Box 32:, Folder 507)
    - A - F, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 508)
    - G - L, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 509)
    - M - R, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 510)
    - S - Z, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 511)
    - Unidentified Author, 1979 (Box 32:, Folder 512)
    - A - F, 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 513)
    - G - L, 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 514)
    - M - R, 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 515)
    - S - Z, 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 516)
    - Unidentified Author, 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 517)
    - A - F, 1981 (Box 32:, Folder 518)
    - G - L, 1981 (Box 33:, Folder 519)
    - M - R, 1981 (Box 33:, Folder 520)
    - S - Z, 1981 (Box 33:, Folder 521)
    - Unidentified Author, 1981 (Box 33:, Folder 522)
    - A - F, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 523)
    - G - L, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 524)
    - M - R, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 525)
    - S - Z, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 526)
    - Unidentified Author, 1982 (Box 33:, Folder 527)
    - A - F, 1983 (Box 33:, Folder 528)
    - G - L, 1983 (Box 33:, Folder 529)
    - M - R, 1983 (Box 33:, Folder 530)
    - S - Z, 1983 (Box 34:, Folder 531)
    - Unidentified Author, 1983 (Box 34:, Folder 532)
      (***1 restricted letter***)
    - A - F, 1984 (Box 34:, Folder 533)
    - G - L, 1984 (Box 34:, Folder 534)
    - M - R, 1984 (Box 34:, Folder 535)
    - S - Z, 1984 (Box 34:, Folder 536)
    - Unidentified Author, 1984 (Box 34:, Folder 537)
    - A - F, 1985 (Box 34:, Folder 538)
    - G - L, 1985 (Box 34:, Folder 539)
    - M - R, 1985 (Box 35:, Folder 540)
    - S - Z, 1985 (Box 35:, Folder 541)
    - Unidentified Author, 1985 (Box 35:, Folder 542)
    - A - F, 1986 (Box 35:, Folder 543)
    - G - L, 1986 (Box 35:, Folder 544)
    - M - R, 1986 (Box 35:, Folder 545)
    - S - Z, 1986 (Box 35:, Folder 546)
    - Unidentified Author, 1986 (Box 36:, Folder 547)
    - A - F, 1987 (Box 36:, Folder 548)
    - G - L, 1987 (Box 36:, Folder 549)
    - M - R, 1987 (Box 36:, Folder 550)
    - S - Z, 1987 (Box 36:, Folder 551)
    - Unidentified Author, 1987 (Box 36:, Folder 552)
    - A - F, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 553)
    - G - L, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 554)
    - M - R, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 555)
    - S - Z, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 556)
    - Unidentified Author, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 557)
    - A - F, 1989 (Box 36:, Folder 558)
    - G - L, 1989 (Box 36:, Folder 559)
    - M - R, 1989 (Box 37:, Folder 560)
    - S - Z, 1989 (Box 37:, Folder 561)
    - Unidentified Author, 1989 (Box 37:, Folder 562)
    - A - F, 1990 (Box 37:, Folder 563)
    - G - L, 1990 (Box 37:, Folder 564)
    - M - R, 1990 (Box 37:, Folder 565)
    - S - Z, 1990 (Box 37:, Folder 566)
    - Unidentified Author, 1990 (Box 37:, Folder 567)
    - A - F, 1991 (Box 37:, Folder 568)
    - G - L, 1991 (Box 37:, Folder 569)
    - M - R, 1991 (Box 37:, Folder 570)
    - S - Z, 1991 (Box 37:, Folder 571)
    - A - F, 1992 (Box 37:, Folder 572)
    - G - L, 1992 (Box 37:, Folder 573)
    - M - R, 1992 (Box 37:, Folder 574)
    - S - Z, 1992 (Box 37:, Folder 575)
    - A - L, 1993 (Box 37:, Folder 576)
    - M - Z, 1993 (Box 37:, Folder 577)
- Series II: Dorn Manuscripts, undated, 1961-1993
  - Subseries A: Poetry, undated, 1961-1974
    - Short Poems (A - Z), undated (Box 37:, Folder 578)
    - Translated Poems (1), undated (Box 37:, Folder 579)
    - Translated Poems (2), undated (Box 28:, Folder 422)
    - Translated Poems (3), undated (Box 28:, Folder 423)
    - Untitled Poem (1), 1966 (Box 37:, Folder 580)
    - Untitled Poem (2) Dorn?, 1970 (Box 37:, Folder 581)
    - Abhorrences Drafts & Originals, undated (Box 38:, Folder 582)
    - Abhorrences Drafts (1), undated (Box 38:, Folder 583)
    - Abhorrences Drafts (2), undated (Box 38:, Folder 584)
    - Abhorrences Drafts (3), undated (Box 38:, Folder 585)
    - Abhorrences Drafts (4), undated (Box 38:, Folder 586)
    - Abhorrences Handscripts, undated (Box 38:, Folder 587)
    - Abhorrences Copy, undated (Box 38:, Folder 588)
    - Abhorrences Typescript, undated (Box 38:, Folder 589)
    - Abhorrences Proofs, undated (Box 38:, Folder 590)
    - Abhorrences Cover Proofs, undated (Box 38:, Folder 591)
    - Book of Poems, 1961-1962 (Box 38:, Folder 592)
    - Captain Jack's Chaps Proofs, undated (Box 28:, Folder 424)
    - Collected Gran Apachería 2nd Edition Copy, undated (Box 38:, Folder 593)
    - The Cosmology of Finding Your Spot, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 425)
    - The Cosmology of Finding Your Spot Final Galley Proofs, 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 594)
    - The Cycle Manuscript, 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 595)
    - The Cycle Typescript (1), 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 596)
    - The Cycle Typescript (2), 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 597)
    - The Cycle Published Edition, undated (Box 28:, Folder 426)
    - Geography Galley Proofs, 1965 (Box 28:, Folder 427)
    - Gran Apachería Proofs, undated (Box 38:, Folder 598)
    - Gran Apachería Galleys, undated (Box 28:, Folder 428)
    - Gunslinger Notes, undated (Box 38:, Folder 599)
    - Gunslinger I-IIII Galleys, undated (Box 28:, Folder 429)
    - Gunslinger I & II Draft, undated (Box 28:, Folder 430)
    - Gunslinger I & II Photocopy, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 431)
    - Gunslinger I Galley Proofs, 1968 (Box 28:, Folder 432)
    - Gunslinger II “ Song #2”, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 433)
    - Gunslinger II “ Gunslinger Questions a Traveling P.H.D.” Typescript, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 600)
    - Gunslinger II Manuscript, 1968-1969 (Box 28:, Folder 434)
    - Gunslinger II Typescript, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 435)
    - Gunslinger II “ Dedication”, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 436)
    - Gunslinger III “ Report GX & C” Typescript 1st Draft, undated (Box 38:, Folder 601)
    - Gunslinger III “ Report GX & C” Typescript 2nd Draft, undated (Box 38:, Folder 602)
    - Gunslinger III Typescript, 1970-1971 (Box 38:, Folder 603)
    - Gunslinger III Typescript Photocopy, 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 604)
    - Gunslinger III Annotated Book, undated (Box 28:, Folder 437)
    - Gunslinger IIII “ Song of Cocaine Lil”, 1969-1970 (Box 28:, Folder 438)
    - Gunslinger IIII “ Zlinger IIII”, undated (Box 28:, Folder 439)
    - Gunslinger IV “ Idling with Observation...” Galley Proofs, 1971 (Box 28:, Folder 440)
    - Gunslinger IV “ Idling with Observation and Song”, 1972 (Box 38:, Folder 605)
    - Hands Up Manuscript, Signed, 1966? (Box 38:, Folder 606)
    - Hands Up “ The Tepee at Tomah” Galley Proof, 1968 (Box 38:, Folder 607)
    - The Newly Fallen Galley Proofs, 1961 (Box 28:, Folder 441)
    - North Atlantic Turbine Typescript, 1966 (Box 28:, Folder 442)
    - North Atlantic Turbine Galley Proofs, undated (Box 28:, Folder 443)
    - North Atlantic Turbine Introduction?, 1967 (Box 38:, Folder 608)
    - Osawatomie Dorn?, 1970 (Box 38:, Folder 609)
    - Recollections of Gran Apachería Draft (1), 1973? (Box 38:, Folder 610)
    - Recollections of Gran Apachería Draft (2), 1973? (Box 38:, Folder 611)
    - Recollections of Gran Apachería Typescript, 1973 (Box 38:, Folder 612)
    - Recollections of Gran Apachería Page Proofs, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Recollections of Gran Apachería Cover, undated (Box 38:, Folder 613)
    - Songs Set Two: A Short Count, 1970 (Box 38:, Folder 614)
    - To Tom Pickard and the Newcastle..., 1968 (Box 28:, Folder 444)
    - Tree Between Two Walls Typescript Translation, 1968 (Box 38:, Folder 615)
    - 24 Love Songs First 10, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 616)
    - 24 Love Songs Typescript, 1969 (Box 38:, Folder 617)
    - 24 Love Songs “ Dedication”, 1969 (Box 28:, Folder 445)
    - Yellow Lola Galleys (1), undated (Box 28:, Folder 446)
    - Yellow Lola Galleys (2), undated (Box 28:, Folder 447)
    - Yellow Lola Materials, undated (Box 38:, Folder 618)
  - Subseries B: Prose, undated, 1965-1990
    - Short Prose (A - Z), undated (Box 38:, Folder 619)
    - Untitled Prose, undated (Box 28:, Folder 448)
    - Abilene, Abilene Copy, undated (Box 28:, Folder 449)
    - Abilene, Abilene Galleys, undated (Box 38:, Folder 620)
    - Al Cohen Construction Co. Copy, undated (Box 28:, Folder 450)
    - American Poetry Archive Film Transcript, undated (Box 38:, Folder 621)
    - Book of Daniel Drew Introduction, 1968 (Box 28:, Folder 451)
    - Boulder Memorial Hospital Copy, undated (Box 38:, Folder 622)
    - Day Report from Day & Night, 1971 (Box 38:, Folder 623)
    - Driving Across the Prairie Published Copy, undated (Box 38:, Folder 624)
    - High Plains Introduction (1), undated (Box 38:, Folder 625)
    - High Plains Introduction (2), undated (Box 38:, Folder 626)
    - Interview of Amiri Baraka, undated (Box 38:, Folder 627)
    - Interview of Tom Clark, undated (Box 38:, Folder 628)
    - Interview of Robert Emmitt, undated (Box 38:, Folder 629)
    - Interview of George Kimball, undated (Box 38:, Folder 630)
    - Interview of Omer Stewart, undated (Box 38:, Folder 631)
    - The Invisible Insurrection Typescript Introduction, 1968 (Box 28:, Folder 452)
    - The Man Who Invented Walt Whitman Faculty Seminar, 1985 (Box 38:, Folder 632)
    - To Max Douglas Introduction, 1974 (Box 28:, Folder 453)
    - The Poet, The People, The Spirit Berkeley Lecture, 1965? (Box 38:, Folder 633)
    - Shoshoneans Typescript, 1965 (Box 38:, Folder 634)
    - Shoshoni 1st Draft, 1965 (Box 38:, Folder 635)
    - Some Business... Published Prose, 1971 (Box 28:, Folder 454)
    - Some Business... Galley Proofs, undated (Box 38:, Folder 636)
    - Some Business... Published Copy, undated (Box 38:, Folder 637)
    - South Park, undated (Box 38:, Folder 638)
    - Tenth Havana International Film Festival, 1988 (Box 38:, Folder 639)
    - Tribute to Richard Bautigan Drafts, 1985 (Box 38:, Folder 640)
    - Unfinished Film Script, undated (Box 28:, Folder 455)
    - Vanishing Lobo Introduction, 1990? (Box 38:, Folder 641)
    - Views Typescript, 1980 (Box 38:, Folder 642)
    - What I See in the Maximus Poems Galley Proofs, 1973 (Box 38:, Folder 643)
  - Subseries C: Notebooks and Calendars, undated, 1966-1993
    - Notebook Efficiency, undated (Box 39)
      (Spiral bound notebook with notes and poems)
    - Notebook Poems 1966
      (Blue notebook with “English Poems 1966” inscribed on first page. Contains approximately 75 pages of poems)
    - Notebook Untitled, 1968?
      (Maroon notebook with mimeographed poem by Charles Olson, dated Feb. 2, 1968, pasted on the inside of the front cover. Contains approximately 31 pages of holograph notes, poems, essays, etc.)
    - Notebook Untitled, 1968-1975
      (4to. black notebook with poems and notes)
    - Notebook Challenge, 1968-1970
      (“Love Songs 1968-1970” inscribed on first page. 8vo. blue notebook with approximately 60 pages of holograph notes)
    - Notebook Untitled, 1969-1993
      (Red notebook with poems, pictures, notes, etc.)
    - Notebook Untitled, 1970
      (Blue notebook with notes and poems)
    - Notebook Daily Reminder 1971 Jennifer Dorn
      (8vo. red notebook with approximately 200 pages by Jennifer Dorn)
    - Notebook Stetson, 1971-1990 (Box 40)
      (Blue notebook with poems, notes, newspaper clippings, pictures, etc.)
    - Notebook Thor, 1971
      (“1971 Days and Night Rept.” inscribed on first page. 8vo. notebook covered in Thor comic book wrapper with approximately 200 pages. Contains calendar of days, appointments, addresses, thoughts, poems, clippings, photographs, etc.)
    - Calendar, 1972-1973
    - Notebook Untitled Jennifer Dorn, 1972?
      (8vo. flowered cloth notebook with approximately 200 pages of poems, thoughts, drawings, photographs, etc. by Jennifer Dorn)
    - Notebook The Iconic Record (contains inserts), 1972 (Box 41)
      (Ledger size notebook with notes by Edward Dorn. Also includes poems, drawings, collages, newspaper clippings, letters, telegrams, etc.)
    - Notebook Mex (contains inserts), 1972
      (“The BK I & II Notebook...A Mexico Scrapbook for Kidd and Maya” inscribed on front page. 8vo. black and white cloth notebook contains approximately 200 pages of poems, collages, newspaper clippings, telegrams, maps, flowers, photographs, etc.)
    - Calendar, 1973-1974
    - Notebook Daily Reminder 1974 Jennifer Dorn
      (8vo. red notebook with entries from January to June by Jennifer Dorn)
    - Notebook Dataday Diary, 1975 (Box 42)
      (8vo. maroon cloth notebook with approximately 100 pages)
    - Calendar, 1976
    - Notebook Untitled, 1978-1987
      (4to. red notebook with approximately 150 pages of holograph notes)
    - Notebook Pen-Tab, 1979
    - Notebook Journal, 1981-1987
      (8vo. red spiral bound notebook with approximately 100 pages of holograph notes)
    - Notebook The Joy of Nothing, 1981-1993
      (Notebook contains notes, poems, rewrites, etc.)
    - Notebook Record Abhorrences, 1983-1986
      (Black and maroon notebook containing poems, notes, drawings, etc.)
    - Notebook Abhorrences, 1984-1985
      (Black and white notebook with poems and notes.)
    - Notebook Hotel Anthony Wayne, 1985-1991
      (4to. blue notebook with picture of Hotel Anthony Wayne pasted on front cover. Contains notes and poems)
    - Notebook Untitled (1), 1988 (Box 43)
      (4to. black notebook with notes and poems)
    - Notebook Untitled (2), 1988
      (4to. black notebook with approximately 100 pages of notes and poems)
    - Notebook The Havana Notebook, 1988
    - Notebook Notes for Elko Cowdo (contains inserts), 1989
      (30 pages of notes for Eldo Cowboy Poetry Festival in January 1989)
- Series III: Dorn Publications, undated, 1972-1991
  - Gunslinger 1 & 2 Plant Inserts, undated (Box 44:, Folder 644)
  - Subseries A: Bean News, undated, 1972-1973
    - Bean News?, undated (Box 44:, Folder 645)
    - Bean News Art?, undated (Box 44:, Folder 646)
    - Bean News #2, undated (Box 44:, Folder 647)
    - Bean News #3, undated (Box 44:, Folder 648)
    - Bean News, undated (Box 44:, Folder 649)
    - Bean News? Galleys (1), undated (Box 28:, Folder 456)
    - Bean News Galleys (2), undated (Box 28:, Folder 457)
    - Bean News Galleys (3), undated (Box 28:, Folder 458)
    - Bean News Stationery, undated (Box 44:, Folder 650)
    - Flyswatter Fans, undated (Box 44:, Folder 651)
    - Tax Coupons, undated (Box 44:, Folder 652)
    - Bean News Batty, Dotty, undated (Box 44:, Folder 653)
    - Bean News Colton, Walter, 1973 (Box 44:, Folder 654)
    - Bean News Darwin, Erasmus, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 655)
    - Bean News Dawson, Fielding, undated (Box 44:, Folder 656)
    - Bean News Prynne, J. H., 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 657)
    - Bean News Waldeman, Anne, undated (Box 44:, Folder 658)
    - Bean News Published Edition (Box 29)
  - Subseries B: Rolling Stock, undated, ca. 1980-1991
    - R. S. Index 1 - 10, undated (Box 44:, Folder 659)
    - R. S. #1 Material, undated (Box 44:, Folder 660)
    - Rolling Stock #1 Published Edition, 1980s (Box 29)
    - R. S. #2 Material, undated (Box 44:, Folder 661)
    - R. S. #2 Originals & Drafts, undated (Box 44:, Folder 662)
    - R. S. #2 Copy (1), undated (Box 44:, Folder 663)
    - R. S. #2 Copy (2), undated (Box 44:, Folder 664)
    - R. S. #2 Copy (3), undated (Box 44:, Folder 665)
    - R. S. #2 Proofread Copy, undated (Box 44:, Folder 666)
    - Rolling Stock #2 Published Edition, 1980s (Box 29)
    - R. S. #3 Art, undated (Box 44:, Folder 667)
    - Rolling Stock #3 Published Edition, 1980s (Box 29)
    - R. S. #4 First Drafts, undated (Box 44:, Folder 668)
    - R. S. #4 Original Copy, undated (Box 44:, Folder 669)
    - R. S. #4 Art, undated (Box 44:, Folder 670)
    - Rolling Stock #4 Published Edition, 1983 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #5 Original Copy, undated (Box 44:, Folder 671)
    - R. S. #5 Copy, undated (Box 44:, Folder 672)
    - R. S. #5 Typesetter Copy, undated (Box 44:, Folder 673)
    - R. S. #5 Art, undated (Box 44:, Folder 674)
    - Rolling Stock #5 Published Edition, 1983 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #6 Copy (1), undated (Box 44:, Folder 675)
    - R. S. #6 Copy (2), undated (Box 44:, Folder 676)
    - R. S. #6 Original Typescripts, undated (Box 44:, Folder 677)
    - Rolling Stock #6 Published Edition, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Ed Dorn's RS Notebook, 1984-1986 (Box 44:, Folder 678)
    - R. S. #7? Article List, undated (Box 44:, Folder 679)
    - R. S. #7 Original Manuscripts (1), undated (Box 44:, Folder 680)
    - R. S. #7 Original Manuscripts (2), undated (Box 44:, Folder 681)
    - R. S. #7 Art, undated (Box 44:, Folder 682)
    - Rolling Stock #7 Published Edition, 1984 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #8 Copy (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 683)
    - R. S. #8 Copy (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 684)
    - R. S. #8 Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 685)
    - Rolling Stock #8 Published Edition, 1984 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #9 Original Copy, undated (Box 45:, Folder 686)
    - R. S. #9 Copy (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 687)
    - R. S. #9 Copy (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 688)
    - R. S. #9 Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 689)
    - Rolling Stock #9 Published Edition, 1985 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #10 Material, undated (Box 45:, Folder 690)
    - R. S. #10 Original Copy Not Used (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 691)
    - R. S. #10 Original Copy Not Used (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 692)
    - R. S. #10 Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 693)
    - Rolling Stock #10 Published Edition, 1985 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #11 Drafts (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 694)
    - R. S. #11 Drafts (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 695)
    - R. S. #11 Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 696)
    - Rolling Stock #11 Published Edition, 1986 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #12 Int. Drafts (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 697)
    - R. S. #12 Int. Drafts (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 698)
    - R. S. #12 Int. Drafts (3), undated (Box 45:, Folder 699)
    - R. s. #12 Int. Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 700)
    - Rolling Stock #12 International Published Edition, 1986 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #13 Manuscripts (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 701)
    - R. S. #13 Manuscripts (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 702)
    - R. S. #13 Art, undated (Box 45:, Folder 703)
    - Rolling Stock #13 Published Edition, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Churchill, Ward R.S. #14 Article, undated (Box 45:, Folder 704)
    - R. S. #14 Material (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 705)
    - R. S. #14 Material (2), undated (Box 45:, Folder 706)
    - R. S. #14 Material (3), undated (Box 45:, Folder 707)
    - R. S. #14 Art (1), undated (Box 45:, Folder 708)
    - R. S. #14 Art (2), undated (Box 29)
    - Rolling Stock #14 Published Edition, 1987 (Box 29)
    - R. S. #15/16 Originals (1), undated (Box 46:, Folder 709)
    - R. S. #15/16 Originals (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 710)
    - R. S. #15/16 Originals (3), undated (Box 46:, Folder 711)
    - R. S. #15/16 Originals (4), undated (Box 46:, Folder 712)
    - R. S. #15/16 Typeset Copy (1), undated (Box 46:, Folder 713)
    - R. S. #15/16 Typeset Copy (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 714)
    - R. S. #15/16 Art, undated (Box 46:, Folder 715)
    - Rolling Stock #15/16 Published Edition, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Rolling Stock #17/18 Published Edition, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Rolling Stock #19/20 Published Edition, 1991 (Box 29)
    - R. S. Rejects, undated (Box 46:, Folder 716)
- Series IV: Publications About Edward Dorn, undated, 1982
  - Unidentified Author Essay, undated (Box 46:, Folder 717)
  - Shoshoneans Book Reviews, undated (Box 46:, Folder 718)
  - Alpert, Barry Interview, undated (Box 46:, Folder 719)
  - Bent, Kim Play, undated (Box 46:, Folder 720)
  - Bezner, Kevin Interview, undated (Box 46:, Folder 721)
  - Boston Phoenix Poem, undated (Box 46:, Folder 722)
  - Clark, Tom Biography, undated (Box 46:, Folder 723)
  - Clark, Tom Book Review, undated (Box 46:, Folder 724)
  - Contemporary Literature Interview, undated (Box 46:, Folder 725)
  - Dog Stories Interview, undated (Box 46:, Folder 726)
  - Fox, Skip Bibliography, undated (Box 46:, Folder 727)
  - Garson, Paul Essay, undated (Box 46:, Folder 728)
  - Haut, Woody Chapter (1), undated (Box 46:, Folder 729)
  - Haut, Woody Chapter (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 730)
  - Herald Journal Article, undated (Box 46:, Folder 731)
  - Kadlecek, John Article, undated (Box 46:, Folder 732)
  - McGrath, Tom Article, undated (Box 46:, Folder 733)
  - McPheron, William Biography (1), undated (Box 46:, Folder 734)
  - McPheron, William Biography (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 735)
  - McPheron, William Biography (3), undated (Box 46:, Folder 736)
  - Perloff, Marjorie Book Review, undated (Box 46:, Folder 737)
  - Perloff, Marjorie Introduction, undated (Box 46:, Folder 738)
  - Rissman, John Essay, undated (Box 46:, Folder 739)
  - Selerie, Gavin Interview, 1982 (Box 46:, Folder 740)
  - Wesling, Donald Bibliography, undated (Box 46:, Folder 741)
  - Wright, John Interview, undated (Box 46:, Folder 742)
  - Zoretich, Frank Article, undated (Box 46:, Folder 743)
- Series V: Submitted Manuscripts, undated
  - Collected Work Unidentified Author (1), undated (Box 46:, Folder 744)
  - Collected Work Unidentified Author (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 745)
  - Collected Work Unidentified Author (3), undated (Box 46:, Folder 746)
  - Unidentified Interviewer Interview of Omer, undated (Box 46:, Folder 747)
  - Barsamic, David Interview of Cockburn & Said, undated (Box 46:, Folder 748)
  - Brakhage, Stan 12th Telluride Film Festival, undated (Box 46:, Folder 749)
  - Cambridge, Charlie Interview of Ivan Sidney, undated (Box 46:, Folder 750)
  - Clark, Tom Der Tatler, undated (Box 46:, Folder 751)
  - Clark, Tom When the Party's Over, undated (Box 46:, Folder 752)
  - Coleman, Victor The Party, undated (Box 46:, Folder 753)
  - Ginsberg, Allen & Patrick Warner Nicaraguan Poet Conference, undated (Box 46:, Folder 754)
  - Haut, Woody? Interview of Mike Cooley, undated (Box 46:, Folder 755)
  - Haut, Woody? Interview of Ken Livingstone, undated (Box 46:, Folder 756)
  - Linton, Deborah Interview of Tom Clark, undated (Box 46:, Folder 757)
  - Narapa Poetry Wars Documents (1), undated (Box 28:, Folder 459)
  - Narapa Poetry Wars Documents (2), undated (Box 46:, Folder 758)
  - Narapa Poetry Wars Documents (3), undated (Box 46:, Folder 759)
  - Olson, Charles American Poetry Archive Film Transcript, undated (Box 46:, Folder 760)
  - Olson, Charles Maximus II Typescript, undated (Box 46:, Folder 761)
  - Raworth, Tom Infolio, undated (Box 46:, Folder 762)
  - Raworth, Tom Writing, undated (Box 46:, Folder 763)
  - Raworth, Tom Writing Proofs, undated (Box 28:, Folder 460)
  - The Party. Sanders, Ed, undated (Box 46:, Folder 764)
  - Collected Work (A - B), undated (Box 47:, Folder 765)
  - Collected Work (C), undated (Box 47:, Folder 766)
  - Collected Work (D - J), undated (Box 47:, Folder 767)